<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pages on SY@work</title>
    <link>http://yeoserene.github.io/page/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pages on SY@work</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Oct 2019 10:26:27 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://yeoserene.github.io/page/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://yeoserene.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Oct 2019 10:26:27 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://yeoserene.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>I am a research engineer at DSO National Laboratories, Singapore. I am currently visiting at the Natural Language Processing Group at CSAIL, MIT under Prof. Regina Barzilay.
I received a B.Sc (First Class Honours) from National University of Singapore in 2015 where I majored in Statistics &amp;amp; Applied Probability, with a specialization in business and finance statistics.
I am currently working on improving automated fact-checking. Previously, I have worked on projects that involved using correlated Gaussian Processes for heat modelling and online incremental clustering techniques for entity resolution.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>http://yeoserene.github.io/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Oct 2019 10:26:27 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://yeoserene.github.io/projects/</guid>
      <description> Be Calculative A simple calculator app to compare interests across three major banks in Singapore - DBS, OCBC and POSB  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>http://yeoserene.github.io/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Oct 2019 10:26:27 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://yeoserene.github.io/publications/</guid>
      <description> 2019  Towards Debiasing Fact Verification Models Tal Schuster, Darsh J Shah, Yun Jie Serene Yeo, Daniel Filizzola, Enrico Santus, Regina Barzilay To appear in EMNLP-IJCNLP 2019 [ arXiv ]  2017  DP Mixture of Warped Correlated GPs for Individualized Time Series Prediction Yun Jie Serene Yeo, Kian Ming A. Chai, Weiping Priscilla Fan, Si Hui Maureen Lee, Junxian Ong, Poh Ling Tan, Yu Li Lydia Law, Kok-Yong Seng NeurIPS Time Series Workshop 2017 [ PDF ]  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>